



(+852) 6040 8671



shirau@gmail.com



sasconcept.ftp.cc

#### **EDUCATION**

2023

Google UX Design Certificate

Coursera

2006-2008

Multimedia Design & Technology (HD)

Hong Kong Polytechnic University

#### **SKILLS**

#### **User Experience**

- Persona
- Target Audience Journey
- Information Architecture
- Site Mapping
- Wireframe
- User Flows
- Prototyping
- Quality Assurance
- Usability Testing
- Collaboration with Development Teams

#### **Visual Design**

- Mood Board
- Branding
- Interface Design
- Information Design

# SHIRLEYAU UX & UI DESIGNER

DIGITAL PRODUCTS, PRINT PRODUCTS

#### **SUMMARY**

A seasoned digital product designer with over 10 years of experience designing products across various sectors including retail, education, gaming, bank and digital advertisement business. Proficient in user-centered design processes, specializing in rapid prototyping, interaction design and final user interface visual design. Looking to excel in both analytical and creative thinking, and shape better user experience design.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

5.2022 - Present

#### **UX, UI Designer**

Konew FinTech Corporation Limited (2483.HK)

### Loan System, Personal Loan App Design, Property Loan Web Design, Entertainment Platform design

- As a product designer, conduct ongoing research of user interface development best practices
- Build and design prototypes of proposed features in company products
- Come up with user-centered design solutions with project managers and engineers to understand user needs and business requirements

9.2014 - 4.2022

# Advisory Senior UX Designer iClick Interactive Asia Limited (NASDAQ: ICLK)



### B2B Data Analysis Platform, Ad Targeting Platform, Wechat Mini Program, Mobile Ad Landing Webpages

- Build and design prototypes of proposed features in company products
- Come up with user-centered design solutions with teams in Shanghai and Beijing such as project managers and engineers to understand user needs and business requirements
- Collorate with Ctrip on delivering Wechat mini programs to reach out China market
- Online advertisment support: Banner and mobile ad landing page design

1.2014 - 6.2014

#### **UI & UX Designer**

#### nBition Development Limited



#### **Mobile Game Apps, Marketing Materials**

- Work closely with the team to design user interfaces of mobile phone applications (games & apps) and reponsive websites. Deliverables included research, interaction flow, wireframes, prototype and final visual design
- Handling projects from concept to production with project manager and developers
- App review and provide recommendations after launching apps to the marketplace

5.2013 - 12.2013

#### **Multimedia Designer**

**Justsolve Consulting Limited** 



#### Andriod Mobile Game Apps, Responsive Web Interface

- Lead designer and work closely with engineers from conceptualization to final visual design
- Directly communicate and organise work milestone with client
- Deliverables included online & offline products: mobile applications user interfaces, flash animation, promotional materials (prints)

6.2012 - 5.2013

## Multimedia Designer Multimedia Global Limited





#### Showcase (Kiosk) Interface, Web Interface

- Work closely with designers, programmers and project managers on mobile phone applications and digital showcases (Kiosk) interfaces, websites and offline marketing materials
- Various client projects including Hang Seng Bank, Sands Macau, Joint Publishing HK...etc

8.2009 - 6.2012

#### Senior Graphic Designer Fingerprint Limited

#### **Graphic, Branding, Printing, Exhibition Material**

- Print design and web design for marketing and branding services
- Communicate and organize the output process and timetable with clients
- Completing tasks by collaborating with junior colleagues

5.2008 - 7.2009

**Graphic Designer Suncolor Limited** 

### SUNCOLOR PRINTING CO., LTD.

**FINGER**PRINT

#### Graphic, Branding, Print Design Products

- · Print design and web design for marketing and branding services.
- Printing composing and directly deal with clients' technical output problems

#### **TOOLS**

- Figma
- Sketch
- Axure RP9
- Invision
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe After Effect
- Adobe InDesign

#### **LANGUAGES**

### **Cantonese**Mother Language

### English

Basic Speaking Fluent Writing

#### Mandarin

<u>F</u>luent